http://www.getabag.com/privacy-policy

Fast Shipping Guaranteed. No minimum order quantity*
Checkout As Guest or Create Account below.
Questions? Call (717) 949-8435
ClearBackpacksRollingSchoolDrawstringLeatherSlingFanny PacksWalletsMen'sWomen'sCheckbookID HoldersNeckCoin HoldersCoolersLunchToteRollingChairBottleSoft SidedCamoTotesDiaperLeatherRollingCottonGroceryFoldableZipperedShoppingUtilityBusinessMessengerLeatherPadfolioLeatherZipperedJunior3 RingPortfolioSample CasesBriefcaseGunRifleHandgunAccessoriesDuffleSportLeatherRollingAll PurposeTravelLuggageGarmentRollingToiletry KitsShoeAccessoriesHandbagsToolPicnicAutoMobileiPadTabletSpeaker
Brands
Andrew PhilipsBellinoBrookstoneCanyon OutbackG-TechPeekaboo & CoHeritage SupplyIglooLife in MotionTravis & Wells
Previous
Next
Recent Posts
Soft-sided versus Hard-sided Coolers
January 20th, 2017
If you ever had a hard time deciding whether you need a soft-sided or hard-sided cooler this artic...
Read More
Clear Bags and Security Checkpoints 101
August 1st, 2016
Do security checkpoints make you anxious or nervous? If so, you’re not alone. Even those with no...
Read More
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY Getabag.com respects your privacy and pledges to earn and keep your trust. All personal information you give us is kept confidential and protected with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. Additionally, we will not sell any of your information to a third party. Occasionally we track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous.
Information About UsContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyConditions of UseLearning CenterFAQ's
My Account Login / Create AccountTrack OrderOrder HistoryView Address BookVisit Cart
Follow Us Facebook Twitter Google+ Pintrest InstagramYouTube Blog
Newsletter Signup
* indicates required
Email Address
*
Call Us (717) 949-8435Hours: 8:30 AM - 6:00 PM EST
*No minimum order quantity on most products.
© 2019 Get A Bag. All Rights Reserved. Powered by Warhead
Our website uses cookies to make your browsing experience better. By using our site you agree to our use of cookies. Learn More
I Agree
×
What Are Cookies
As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.
For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.
How We Use Cookies
We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.
Disabling Cookies
You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.
The Cookies We Set
Account related cookies
If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.
Login related cookies
We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.
Form related cookies
When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.
Site preference cookies
In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Third Party Cookies
In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.
This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.
For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.
We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with social network in various ways. For these to work, the social networks may set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site, or contribute to other purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.
